### **DAYAMI SILVIA EMORY**

2977 McFarlane Road Miami, FL 33133 Cell Phone: 786.346.8267

E-Mail: Dayami.Emory@gmail.com

### **CAREER GOALS**

With an objective to continue my career in human resources management, I have learned through over 8 years of HR experience, three core segments of business operations: strategic workforce planning, employee engagement, and talent management. These selected experiences will allow me to relate with, lead, and direct employees, combined with creating an efficient and cost-effective business. In my view, human resources is all about integrity, transparency, and crafting a healthy work environment.

### **EDUCATION**

University of Central Florida - Orlando, FL

August 2011

Bachelor of Arts, Business Administration • Overall Cumulative GPA: (3.75/4.0) - Cum Laude

March 2018

University of Colorado- Global Campus

Master's in Human Resource Management • Overall Cumulative GPA: (3.8/4.0) Magna Cum Laude

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Assistant Vice President-Human Resources Generalist**

EFG Capital International Corp.: Miami, Fl

August 2019- Present

- Lead a team of over 300 employees between LATAM and the Caribbean
- Responsible for all New Hire Implementation and processes
- Conduct entire interview process for all managers and open positions
- Prepare and execute wellness initiatives and all employee events
- Responsible for all Benefit administration and implementation
- Run entire payroll administration for multiple entities
- Responsible for all employee relations matters
- Responsible for building and enhancing processes to achieve more automated functions
- Run all performance management and succession planning

### **Assistant Vice President-Human Resources Generalist**

September 2014 - August 2019

Apollo Bank: Miami, Fl -Florida Trend Magazine- Best Places to Work

- Lead a team of 95 employees as the Interim Human Resources Director for over 6 months
- Developed and implemented employee recognition program
- Organized and executed all employee engagement and team building events
- Conducted new hire orientations and exit interviews
- Responsible for employee communications, benefit administration and maintaining employee files and records.
- Responsible for payroll administration, employee relations & culture development
- Counseled and advised employees and managers on internal employee relations practices

## **Human Resources Assistant and Account Manager**

December 2012 - August 2014

Acordis International Corporation: Pembroke Pines, FL – One of Inc. 5,000 fastest growing company in the United States

- Responsible for assisting HR Manager in all Human resources functions from onboarding to exit interviews
- Developing and implementing new training and development for all employees and new hires
- Responsible for attending recruiting events such as career fairs in order to identify top talent
- Maintaining relationships with major office solution providers such as IBM, Cisco, Xerox, HP with the purpose of not
  only understanding the various products, furthermore understanding the economics and cost structure for their
  products
- Handling and analyzing leasing agreements for office managers to determine the best financing option

### **Human Resources Consultant**

November 2011 – October 2012

Paycom Payroll: Miami, FL – 4<sup>th</sup> largest payroll services company focused on mid-sized businesses

- Conducted one-on-one training sessions with Human Resources Representatives from premier companies to introduce and integrate applicant tracking, benefit administration, E-verify, COBRA, time and attendance, payroll, and HRIS tracking
- Developed weekly presentations via PowerPoint to train peers across a multitude of competitors systems such as ADP and Paychex

- Developed and produced detailed comparative analysis of alternative human resource systems, including cost, functionality, and ease of integration analysis
- Lead and influenced CFO's, Controllers, Human Resources managers, and other client executives to integrate Paycom into their business model by providing solutions to eliminate manual processes

# **Management Trainee Associate**

# June 2009 - November 2011

Cintas Corporation: Orlando & Miami, FL – Fortune 500 specialized consumer service company

- Assisted Senior Management and HR Managers with ongoing projects such as cash control, customer billing, asset management, payroll, and reporting
- Determined utilization capacity of the stockroom by managing inventory and maintaining budget control
- Lead and motivated a 10 person team of associates that lowered material costs by 5%
- Created marketing proposals for current and prospective clients to increase company revenue
- Initiated and maintained long-term relationships with a variety of local businesses

## **SKILLS**

- Bilingual English/Spanish, Fluency and comprehension (verbal and written)
- Human Resources Certification- Miami Dade College
- Proficient in Microsoft Office
- Lean Six Sigma Greenbelt Certified
- HRIS Applications (ADP, Paychex, Fidelity)